Stacy A. Pierson, PharmD

Pharmacist

Cherry Hill, NJ - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/b395dd24352d729a

Doctor of Pharmacy with 10 years of retail experience looking to pursue a career that allows me the opportunity to utilize my clinical and patient counseling skills. I also have a history in long term care pharmacy and a great interest in geriatrics and medical writing.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Pharmacist

Superfresh - Westmont, NJ - May 2003 to Present

Retail staff pharmacist in grocery store setting. Worked without the aid of technicians, which allowed for great interpersonal relationships/ one on one counseling sessions with patients. Acted as preceptor for multiple 6th year pharmacy students. Was written up in company newsletter for projects done with students. Licensed immunizer. Acted as pharmacy manager from 2010 to 2011.

Staff Pharmacist

Walgreens - Southern NJ - October 2002 to May 2003

Worked various locations as pharmacist floater.

Pharmacy Tech/Intern

Partners Pharmacy - Cranford, NJ - June 1999 to August 2002

Called nursing homes for order verification. Performed double check of 24-hour unit dose cassettes and emergency kits. Filled 30-day bingo card and Artromik box orders. Was responsible for compounding and keeping inventory of external medications.

Student Tutor

The University of the Sciences in Philadelphia - Philadelphia, PA - January 1998 to May 2001

Helped students with writing class assignments and resumes. Prepared students for Writing Proficiency Examination. Provided weekly tutoring sessions with ESL students for writing.

Pharmacist

Pharma

EDUCATION

PharmD in Pharmacy

University of the Sciences - Philadelphia, PA 1996 to 2002

SKILLS

Immunization, PDX, McKesson Enterprise, Apple, Microsoft

CERTIFICATIONS

Licensed Immunizer